

CONTACT

- **** 01773242352
- ✓ mdsajedulislambrur@gmail.com
- Park more, Rangpur
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/md-sajedul-islam-963aa5251
- https://www.facebook.com/share/1Bf8nvXkyn/

EDUCATION

Begum Rokeya University, Rangpur

 Master's of Mass communication and journalism (Running)

Begum Rokeya University, Rangpur

 Bachelor of Mass communication and journalism(2019-2020)

H.S.C:Carmichael College, Rangpur

Board :Dinajpur Passing Year :2019

S.S.C: Afanullah High School, Mahigoni, Rangpur

Board :Dinajpur Passing Year :2017

SKILLS

- Content writing
- · News gathering and writing
- · Project Management
- Feature writing
- Public Relations
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- · Critical Thinking

Md.Sajedul Islam

Journalism Enthusiast | Content writer

About Me

I have completed my Bachelor's degree in Mass Communication and Journalism from Begum Rokeya University, Rangpur. Alongside my studies, I have worked as a campus correspondent for local, national, and online newspapers for three years. Additionally, I have been actively involved with several organizations, where I successfully demonstrated teamwork and fulfilled various responsibilities. I am eager to contribute and grow professionally in the field of media and communication.

Career Objective

To utilize my creative skills and acquired experience in the field of media and communication by contributing to a professional organization and achieving personal and organizational growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Protidiner Bangladesh

BRUR, Campus Correspondent

Bayannor Alo(Local media)
BRUR, Campus Correspondent

Rising BD

Campus Correspondent

The Campus Today

Campus Correspondent

Naye Odhikar Transgender Unnovon Sanggostha (6 months) 2024

ARTICLE 19 (project organised)

CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Joint Secretary

Begum Rokeya University journalist Association

General Secretary

Brahmaputra Education Welfare Council, Jatrapur, Kurigram Sadar

- General Member
 Swapasiri,BRUR
- General member Rotaract Club,Rangpur Central

Associate Editor
Bangladesh journalism students
Council central, Dhaka

2024 - PRESENT

2022- PRESENT

2023 - 2024

2022

Vice President

Shuprovat, BRUR

- General Member

 Prothom Alo

 Bondhusova, Rangpur
- General Member Earth Club, BRUR

ACHIEVEMENT

- MRDI Certificate
- Bondhusova certificate

Computer training Certificate

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Microsoft office
- (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- Managing Digital platform
- Video editing (Canva)
- News gathering and editing

LANGUAGES

- English
- Bengali

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of birth: 22/11/2002 Nationality:Bangladeshi

Religion :Islam Permanent Address :

Jatrapur, Kurigram Sadar

TRAININGS AND WORKSHOPS

Workshop on Fact checking and Digital hygiene Organisation: MRDI

Workshop on Civic Engagement and Human Rights

Organisation: Article 19 South Asia and Plan International Bangladesh

Follow up and implementation of UPR recommendations Organisation: Article 19

Validating workshop on Civic space report
 Organisation: Article 19

VOLUNTEERING AND SOCIAL WORK

Organisation: Better Future Bangladesh

Experience: Relief distribution, Conducting awareness campaigns

Organisation: Prothom Alo Bondhsova

Experience: Math Olympiad

Organisation: Rotaract Club

Experience: Relief distribution

REFERENCE

Dr.Md.Nazrul Islam

Associate Professor Department of Mass Communication and Journalism

Begum Rokeya University, Rangpur

Phone: 8801717088781 **Email:** nazrul312@brur.ac.bd

Sarwar Ahmed

Assistant Professor
Department of Mass Communication
and Journalism

Begum Rokeya University, Rangpur

Phone: 01913958190

DECLARATION

I certify that the above-mentioned information is accurate and complete to the best of my knowledge.